All my life you have been faithful
All my life you have been so, so good
With every breath that I am able
I sing of the goodness of God
(音樂結束)
(電話響起)
Your goodness is running after, is running after me
With my life laid down and surrendered now
I'll give you everything
Your goodness is running after, is running after me
With my life laid down and surrendered now
I'll give you everything
Your goodness is running after, is running after me
With my life laid down and surrendered now
I'll give you everything
Your goodness is running after, is running after me
(音樂結束)
(我愛你)
Oh my love you have been so, so good
With every breath that I am able
And I will sing of the goodness of God
OK
(電話響起)
(我愛你)
Testing, testing, one, two, three
Testing, testing
咦,咁我點知得唔得呀
喺入面嘢
Testing
試咗呀
(我愛你)
然後就是要把這個電話給電話中心的那個人,然後他就會給你一個電話號碼,然後你就可以直接直接去接他。
然後就可以直接接到電話。
然後你就可以直接接到電話。
然後你就可以直接接到電話號碼。
然後你可以直接接到電話號碼。
(音樂)
大相思
: